# Katja Zenker

JUNIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

**Portfolio** 

Address.
Prague / Czech Republic

+420 773 247 883

Email. katjazenker@gmail.com

https://www.queuing4oranges.com

## **PROFILE**

Junior Web Developer experienced in working with FE technologies (HTML, CSS, JavaScript and ReactJS) as well as BE technologies (PHP, Laravel). A passionate, dedicated and patient individual, who likes working in a multilingual and multicultural environment (on-site or remotely). As former educator, highly self-organized, used to working within tight deadlines and collaborating with different parties.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# 2023 - today Junior JavaScript Developer (TeskaLabs Ltd)

Developing and maintaining the UI of software products with focus on cyber security. JavaScript/ReactJS / Git / Docker / Linux / Agile.

## 2022-2023 WEB DEVELOPER (freelance/volunteer)

Planning and developing small sized websites and web apps for individuals and start ups.

ReactJS, PHP, Git, Figma, UX, UI

www.altira.cz www.lesbotoc.cz

## 2011-2022 FREELANCE GERMAN TEACHER (corporate + private)

Planning, preparing, delivering lessons for individual students with focus on administative tasks, presentations, workflow, work environment and communication.

## 2008-2022 FREELANCE GERMAN TEACHER (corporate)

Planning, preparing, delivering lessons for companies with a strong focus on business German in the field of Automotive, IT and Finance.

## **EDUCATIONAL**

# 2023 React 18 Tutorial and Projects Course (2023) (Udemy)

Microfrontends with React: A Complete Developer's Guide (Udemy)

## 2022 PHP | Build a Complete API (Udemy)

Complete Web Design: from Figma to Webflow (Udemy)

Build Website with React & Firebase (Net Ninja)

## 2022 DATA4YOU PRAGUE- Web Development Bootcamp

60 hours pre-studies, 12 weeks bootcamp (every day consisting of 8 hours studying in school + 4 hours of self-study), 4 group hackathons, 1 final group project

tech stack: HTML, CSS/Sass, Git, JavaScript, React, PHP, OOP in PHP, MySQL, API, Laravel, Command line, Gulp, Responsive Web, Intro to SEO

## 2014 HOCHSCHULE ZITTAU/GÖRLITZ (B.A. in Social Work)

Learning and developing a wide range of softskills - ability to work and communicate clearly with people, being highly organized and effective, critical thinking.

### **SKILLS**

HTML 5 - CSS/Sass - JavaScript - ReactJS - Bootstrap - Responsive Web PHP - Laravel - MySQL Git - Webpack - Linux Agile - Teamwork

## **LANGUAGES**

German (native), English (C2), Czech (B2), French (A1)

## **HOBBIES**

CrossFit, Weightlifting. Photography. Creating things.





